[
  {
    "question": "What is Dans' surname",
    "choice1": "Ngo",
    "choice2": "Nguyen",
    "choice3": "Le",
    "choice4": "Tran",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "When is Dans' Birthday?",
    "choice1": "April 10",
    "choice2": "December 22",
    "choice3": "May 28",
    "choice4": "October 12",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": " What school does Dan go to?",
    "choice1": "Bonnyrigg High School",
    "choice2": "Prairewood High School",
    "choice3": "St John's Park High School",
    "choice4": "Canley Vale High School",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is Dan?",
    "choice1": "15",
    "choice2": "16",
    "choice3": "14",
    "choice4": "19",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dans' Dad's name?",
    "choice1": "Hoang",
    "choice2": "Tam",
    "choice3": "Con",
    "choice4": "Vinh",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How many brother or sisters does Dan have?",
    "choice1": "1",
    "choice2": "2",
    "choice3": "3",
    "choice4": "3",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which game is Dan's favourite game?",
    "choice1": "Clash Royale",
    "choice2": "League of Legends",
    "choice3": "Roblox",
    "choice4": "Valorant",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What champion does Dan main in League of Legends?",
    "choice1": "Yasuo",
    "choice2": "Yone",
    "choice3": "Akali",
    "choice4": "Does not main a champion",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was Dan's first friend in high school?",
    "choice1": "David",
    "choice2": "Ethan C",
    "choice3": "James",
    "choice4": "Jayden",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How tall is Dan?(according to David)",
    "choice1": "180cm",
    "choice2": "178cm",
    "choice3": "177cm",
    "choice4": "179cm",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which hand is Dan's dominant hand?",
    "choice1": "Right",
    "choice2": "Left",
    "choice3": "Ambidextrous",
    "choice4": "Does not have hands",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dan's favourite food?",
    "choice1": "Pizza",
    "choice2": "Udon",
    "choice3": "Pho",
    "choice4": "Chicken nuggets",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dan's Net worth?",
    "choice1": "$20 million",
    "choice2": "$500 thousand",
    "choice3": "$0",
    "choice4": "$5",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What Nationality is Dan?",
    "choice1": "Chinese",
    "choice2": "Japanese",
    "choice3": "Korean",
    "choice4": "Vietnamese",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dan's shoe size?",
    "choice1": "UK 9",
    "choice2": "US 9",
    "choice3": "US 11",
    "choice4": "UK 10",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dan's favourite Clash Royale Card?",
    "choice1": "Mini Pekka",
    "choice2": "Arrows",
    "choice3": "Tesla",
    "choice4": "Goblin barrel",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
